thirstiesbaby.com 2016-11-03

# Legal - Privacy Policy | Thirsties Modern Cloth Diapers!!

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy of Thirsties, Inc. ("Thirsties") describes the privacy practices for Thirsties (the "Privacy Policy").  The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you, including information gathered when you visit a Thirsties website (the "Site"), located at [www.thirstiesbaby.com](https://www.thirstiesbaby.com/), [www.thirstiesoutlet.com](http://www.thirstiesoutlet.com/), or [www.thirstieswholesale.com](http://www.thirstieswholesale.com/), and information we may receive from third parties or affiliates, how we may use that information, whether we disclose that information to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information.  Thirsties strives to help visitors of the Site protect their privacy while using our Site.  By using the Site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**How We Collect and Use Information**

We may collect information in several ways by your use of this Site, as well as from forms you submit to us, or personal correspondence, such as emails or letters that you send to us.  We may ask you to voluntarily provide us with personal information on this Site.  In addition, when you log onto the Site, our servers may log your IP address, the URL of your request and other information that is provided in the HTTP header.  Also, our third-party service providers may ask you voluntarily to provide personal information on their websites and may share such personal information with us, as governed by their respective privacy policies.  Our use of information received from a service provider will be dictated by the service provider's privacy policies and not this Privacy Policy. 

We collect two types of information: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information.  Personally identifiable information is information that identifies you or can be used to identify or contact you ("Personally Identifiable Information").  We also may collect information that by itself typically cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as demographic information (such as age, profession or gender), user IP addresses, browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our Site ("Non-Personally Identifiable Information").

Like many other websites, Thirsties may use cookies to customize content specific to your interests and track your use of the Site.  "Cookies" are text files that are placed on your computer and may be used to store your personal information.  In addition to cookies, Thirsties may use other now known or later developed technologies, to assist Thirsties in observing the behavior of users visiting the Site.  These technologies access individual user information but the information is used only to compile aggregated statistics about the Site's usage. **  **

This Site uses Google Analytics (and in the future may use other similar sites or services), a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"), to better assist Thirsties in understanding how the Site is used.  Google Analytics will place cookies on your computer that will generate information that we select about your use of the Site, including your computer's IP address.  That information will be transmitted to and stored by Google.  The information will be used for the purpose of evaluating consumer use of the Site, compiling reports on Site activity for Thirsties’ use, and providing other services relating to Site activity and usage.  Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf.  You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser.  Please note that by doing so, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Site.  The use of cookies by Google Analytics is covered by [Google's privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html). **    **

Personally Identifiable Information we collect may include your name, email addresses, postal addresses, ZIP code, employer, job title, telephone number, credit card information, date of birth, gender, age, user name and password, pregnancy due date (if applicable), your child’s date of birth, your product preferences, your child’s response to conventional and cloth diapering, and other information either desirable or necessary to provide quality services to our customers and visitors.  We may also collect information about you such as your use of the Site and communication preferences. 

To the extent we are able to do so, we may link your Non-Personally Identifiable Information with your Personally Identifiable Information.  We may also link information collected online with information we collect offline or collected online by third parties.

Thirsties may use the information collected from you to provide services which you have requested from us.  We may also use your personal information to send you targeted messages, publications, news, and information about events, special offers, promotions and benefits.  Thirsties may use third-party service providers to send and distribute e-mail and to perform other marketing and support functions.  We may use information we collect from you to improve the content of this Site, to enhance users' experiences when visiting this Site, and to customize the content and layout of this Site for each individual user. 

**Sharing of Personal Information**

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy or as specifically agreed to by you, we will not disclose any information we gather from you on our Site.  Thirsties may provide your personal information to service providers or contractors to perform functions on its behalf, such as, but not limited to, companies or individuals hired to: communicate news, deliver Thirsties’ promotional materials via e-mail and direct mail, to develop, enhance, market or provide any of Thirsties’ products, to process credit card payments and to assist Thirsties with sending communications and performing other marketing and support functions. Also, Thirsties may use third-party social media platforms, including third-party social media websites, to communicate with you.

We also may share with third parties aggregated demographic and statistical information that is not personally identifiable.

Thirsties also may disclose an individual's personal information:

  * to a person who in the reasonable judgment of Thirsties is seeking the information as an agent of the individual; 
  * in situations where sharing or disclosing your information is required in order to offer you products or services you desire; 
  * to a third party or parties, where disclosure is required or permitted by law; 
  * if, in the reasonable judgment of Thirsties, it is necessary enforce compliance with our internal policies or the [Terms of Use](https://www.thirstiesbaby.com/customer-center/terms-of-use) or to protect our Site, customers, or others; and
  * to any other entity that acquires all or a portion of our organization by merger, reorganization, operation of law, or a sale of some or all of Thirsties’ assets.

Thirsties may be required to use or disclose your information in connection with a legal action or other proceeding, including without limitation, in response to a court order or a subpoena.  We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.

Through the Site, Thirsties may make available areas that allow for user interaction, including blogs, forums, bulletin board services, chat areas, or other message and communications features.  Some of these forums may require registration.  Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Children's Information**

Thirsties does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information on the Site from children under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If Thirsties learns that, despite these measures, a child under the age of 13 has submitted personally identifiable information to Thirsties through the Site, it will take reasonable measures to delete such information from its records and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required by law).

**How We Store Your Information**

Thirsties is committed to protecting the security of any personal information you provide to us.  We maintain commercially reasonable safeguards to maintain the security and privacy of personal information that you provide to us.  After you have submitted your information online to Thirsties, we recommend that you end your browser session before leaving your computer.  In spite of these protections, Thirsties cannot guarantee the security of any data submitted over the Internet.  After your information reaches Thirsties, however, it is stored on servers (or in the case of information received from you in person, in writing or over the phone, in physical storage areas) protected by procedures and technology designed to block reasonably foreseeable intrusions by unauthorized third parties. 

**Opt-Out From Mailings**

From time to time, you may receive periodic mailings, telephone calls or e-mails from Thirsties with news or other information on events, services, discounts, special promotions, upcoming events or other offers from or on behalf of Thirsties.  If at any time you wish to stop receiving emails or mailings from Thirsties please send us an email to support@thirstiesbaby.com, with the phrase "Privacy Opt-out: Thirsties Mailings" in the subject line, or write to us at the address provided below, and we will remove you from Thirsties’ mailing list.  Alternatively, for e-mail communications, you may opt out of receiving such communications by following the unsubscribe instructions set forth at the bottom of most promotional e-mail messages from Thirsties. **  **

**Third-Party Websites**

This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Thirsties.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites that are accessible through this Site, including but not limited to any third-party websites that process payments on behalf of Thirsties.  Please be aware that third-party websites that process payments for Thirsties and websites for our advertisers, sponsors, affiliated entities and other third parties that are accessible through this Site may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.  Thirsties is not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites and will not be responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that you visit. 

**Contact Us**

If you would like to update or correct your information or modify your communication preferences, or if you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy or the use of information collected, you can contact us:

**by email:**  
support@thirstiesbaby.com

**by writing to us at:**  
436 W. 67th St.  
Loveland, CO 80538

**Policy Changes**

Thirsties may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time.  Should this Privacy Policy be amended in any way, changes will be posted to this webpage.  As we may make changes from time to time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy.  Your continued use of the Site after the effective date of any modification to the Privacy Policy will be deemed to be your agreement to the changed terms.

Last Updated:  May 20, 2011
